please sign this
请签署此
Is there anything wrong?
有什么不对的吗。
Wait a moment
等一下
If you don't sign it every morning, I will sign it quickly.
每天早上你不签的话，我就赶紧签。
I know
我知道
Let's sign
我们来签名吧
let's check on my grandson
让我们检查一下我的孙子
what happened?
发生了什么？
This is not Xu Yinian's situation.
这不是徐以年的情况。
This is the surrender report we received.
这是我们收到的投降报告。
now my case is correct
现在我的情况是正确的
he
他
Surrender
自首
port imitator
港口模仿者
Purchase false evidence.
购买虚假证据。
and handling obstruction cases.
以及处理阻碍案件。
Bionic humans have been discovered
仿生人类已经被发现
The police should be responsible for arresting people.
警察应该负责逮捕人。
let him go
放了他
This won't just follow the crowd
这不会随波逐流
We will first investigate cases related to biomimicry.
我们首先会调查与仿生学相关的案例。
handed over to the police again
再次移交给警方
We're still hearing the news. Please leave.
我们仍在听到这个消息。请离开。
please
请
give me 5 minutes
给我5分钟
I told him alone.
我单独告诉他。
please leave
请离开
I ask you
我问你
Cheng Nuo
程諾
Would you sign this yourself?
你自己会签这个吗？
I sign voluntarily
我自愿签字
i don't care about you
我不关心你
Cheng Nuo
程诺
What did I say when you were investigating?
你调查的时候我说什么了？
How will the two of us investigate?
我们两个将如何调查
now you
轮到你了
The test report has been issued
检测报告已出具
Will you solve this case with me?
你愿意和我一起解决这个案子吗？
Please also report to Wanbu.
也请向万部汇报。
3 minutes
3分钟
I know you came here for her.
我知道你是冲着她来的。
But she has passed biometric verification.
但她已经通过了生物识别验证。
I can't help her, and neither can you.
我帮不了她，你也帮不了
No matter what you do it won't change
无论你做什么都不会改变
don't change
不要改变
I know she's a copycat
我知道她是个模仿者
I knew her from the first time I met her.
我从第一次见到她就认识她了。
But what you can change is
但你可以改变的是
Take me there too
带我也去
Before we meet a thought
在我们遇见一念之前
I am alone
我独自一人
Shells floating in the sea
贝壳漂浮在海里
like
好像
I think I saved her
我想我救了她
But the truth is, she didn't save me.
但事实是，她并没有救我。
Now?
现在？
kick her out
把她踢出去
So please take me there.
所以请带我去吧。
if she goes somewhere
如果她去某个地方
where do i want to go
我要去哪里
I will always be with Yi Nian
我会永远和一念在一起
We are looking at bionic animals, not humans.
我们正在寻找的是仿生动物，而不是人类。
Even if I'm locked up
即使我被锁起来
Do you know you can't be locked up together?
你知道你们不能被关在一起吗？
violinist
小提琴家
people
人
You may not be able to tell them apart even with the naked eye.
即使用肉眼你可能也无法区分它们。
Cheng Nuo
程诺
One more, please
请再来一份
Judge me with her
和她一起评判我
At least
至少
i will see her again
我会再次见到她
I can't change anything anymore
我无法再改变一切
You need to fit into your future
你需要融入你的未来
go see her
去见她
Is it worth it?
这值得么？
worth
值得
Arrive in 3 minutes
3分钟后到达
Wait a moment
等一下
I want to say something to her
我想对她说点什么
Sun Yao is here
孙遥来了
I can arrange to meet you
我可以安排和你们见面
but please tell him
但请告诉他
gone
走了
Why
为什么
Isn't it because of him that you came back?
你回来还不是为了他吗？
Sun Yao said
孙尧说
You never rejected him
你从来没有拒绝过他
You just want to make him happy
你只想着让他开心
Do you know Sun Yao works for you?
你知道孙瑶为你工作吗？
how much have you done
你做了多少
your imitation
你的模仿
Maybe you are following your original obsession.
也许你正在按照你最初的执着去做。
what happens now
现在发生什么事
If Sun Chun knew
如果孙春知道的话
If you don't see him before leaving
如果你在离开前没有见到他
How sad he must be
他一定有多伤心
Sun Chun let me go
孙春放开我
but come back
但回来吧
because i saw
因为我看到了
There are many people like you around him.
他周围有很多像你这样的人。
because I
因为我
punish him for his crime
惩罚他的罪行
I know too
我也知道
I will definitely be sent back
我一定会被遣送回来
I think this is the last time
我想这是最后一次
On the other hand I don't want to see you
另一方面我不想见到你
But you still have a chance to meet.
但你们还有机会见面。
believe him
相信他
I'm scared
我很害怕
When I came, I met you again.
当我来的时候，我又遇见了你。
can i see him again and be like this again
我可以再次见到他并再次像这样
I can't stand it anymore
我再也无法忍受了
sorry.
对不起。
Thanks.
谢谢。
I asked Zhou Chen to solve the case.
我让周辰破案了。
this incident
这次事件
Of course this has nothing to do with Yin Tianhong.
这当然与尹天红无关。
you
你
Maybe I'm too persistent
也许是我太执着
The result will be like this
结果会是这样的
this is your role
这就是你的角色
do not think too much
别想太多
Thanks
谢谢
thank you for your signature
谢谢你的签名
I know you don't want to sign either.
我知道你也不想签字。
wholeheartedly
一心是
Cheng Nuo
程诺
you are talking
你在讲话
Xu Niannian believes that he is a bionic person.
许一年认定自己是一个仿生人。
deported
被遣返
we don't even know
我们甚至不知道
What happens to her next?
她之后会发生什么？
No
不
Why
为什么
Cheng Nuo
程诺
She should have been able to live here.
原本她应该可以住在这里的。
Is she guilty?
她有罪吗？
Why did you corner her?
你为什么把她逼到墙角？
Cheng Nuo
程诺
Cheng Nuo’s story
程诺的故事
I always thought
我一直以为
we are all the same person
我们都是同一个人
fear of loneliness
害怕孤独
I thought you would understand how I feel
我以为你会理解我的感受
but i was wrong
但是我错了
you are not a lonely person
你不是一个孤独的人
You are the outcasts
你们是被遗弃的人
your life
你的一生
I don't understand love
我不懂爱
until you die
直到你死
You don’t understand love either
你也不懂爱
Why should we separate?
我们为什么要分开？
Why didn't Cheng Nuo stop him?
程诺为什么不阻止他？
Even if it's the last chance to meet
即使是最后一次见面的机会
Won't you give it to me?
你不肯给我吗？
I know you're not suitable for catching androids
我知道你不适合抓仿生人
Impulsive easily
容易冲动
But you are not a person who does not know what is right.
但你并不是一个不知道什么是对的人。
I know you're having a hard time right now
我知道你现在过得很艰难
But it's not your fault
但这不是你的错
you just finished your work
你刚刚完成你的工作
If it weren't for the Zhou Dynasty, they would
如果不是周朝，他们
when i stare at it
当我盯着它看的时候
You may miss Xu Yinian.
你可能想念许以年。
you think too much
你想太多了
Isn’t it natural to investigate imitators?
调查模仿者不是很自然吗？
nothing is difficult
没有什么是困难的
Why do this?
为什么要这么做？
Why do I always lock myself away?
为什么我总是把自己锁起来？
after recent events
最近发生的事件之后
you have changed
你已经改变
Result#Kekka#
结果#Kekka#
result
結果
In the end you are still the same as before
到最后你还是和以前一样
I looked up violinists
我查了一下小提琴家
I wanted to show it to my mom.
我想把它拿给我妈妈看。
I was the one who needed her attention the most.
我是最需要她关注的人。
but she died
但她死了
Do I still have the right to change?
我还有权利改变吗？
Is this why you ran away?
这就是你逃跑的理由？
You thought you were hiding your heart
你以为你隐藏了你的心
Do I have to face it?
我必须面对吗？
Do you think you know me well?
你觉得你很了解我吗？
if i tell you
如果我告诉你
I killed an android.
我杀了一个仿生人。
You want me to capture the bionics
你想让我抓到仿生生物
Are you sad?
你伤心吗？
Who killed it?
谁杀了它？
Cheng Nuo
程诺
Who did you kill?
你杀了谁？
the time and place it happened
事情发生的时间和地点
Is it important?
是不是重要？
I just think
我只是觉得
if you tell me everything
如果你告诉我一切
might be easier
可能会容易一点
I want to help you
我想帮你
I don't need your help
我不需要你的帮助
Welcome next time
欢迎下次光临
Our eyes have the most practical experience.
我们的眼睛有最实际的经验。
Excellent investigator
优秀调查员
I will share the report with everyone.
我会把报告分享给大家。
what happened
发生了什么
OK
好的
The pressure is mine
压力是我的
I can't say I'm a good investigator.
我不能说我是一个优秀的调查员。
I've had some incidents lately.
我最近遇到了一些事件。
I chose a few words to say.
我选择了几句话要说。
share with everyone
与大家分享
everyone should know
每个人都应该知道
Bionic human body structure
仿生人体结构
No different from us humans
和我们人类没有什么不同
So just use your naked eyes
所以只要用肉眼
indistinguishable
无法区分的
It is our duty to catch them.
我们有责任抓住他们。
For example, these incidents I encountered
比如我遇到的这几个事件
what happened?
发生了什么？
Cheng Nuo
程诺
Mr. Gao is waiting at the front desk.
高先生正在前台等候。
Giving it to him is like giving it to me.
给他就等于给我一样。
give it to me
交给我
This is that video
这是那个视频
oh i'm here
哦，我在这里
It's Takasan.
是塔卡桑。
Yes
是的
I am Cheng Nuo
我是程诺
This is the video I requested
这是我要求的视频
Hello
你好
What about video?
视频呢？
Although he said he would give it to me, I already gave it to him.
虽然他说要给我，但我已经给了他。
Thanks
谢谢
No one has seen this video.
没有人看过这个视频。
not any
没有任何
I got a call from the traffic police
我接到交警的电话
Then he took out his card and came over.
然后他掏出卡走了过来。
Another option is automatic parking logging.
另一种选择是自动停车记录。
I usually don't look at it unless it has scratches.
除非有划痕，否则我通常不会去看它。
Have you copied it?
你抄过吗
not any
没有任何
This is where the surveillance cameras are located directly inside
这是监控摄像头直接位于内部的位置
That is, if we provide clues
也就是说，如果我们提供线索
Is there a reward?
有奖励吧？
Don't worry, I will apply for the fees.
不用担心，费用我会申请的。
Are there any new clues?
有没有新的线索？
No.
没有。
Was Yin Zhenghong in the hospital the day he escaped?
尹正弘逃跑那天是在医院吗？
that's right
这是正确的
The two of us are also helping to catch him.
我们两个人也在帮忙抓他。
Can I have a look?
我可以看一下吗？
Understood
明白了
take a look
看一看
where are you going?
你要去哪里？
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
let us wash our hands
让我们洗手
Are you burning your card?
你烧卡了吗？
Caught in the machine
被机器夹住
are you kidding me?
你在逗我吗？
Who are you protecting?
你在保护谁？
i want to know myself
我想了解我自己
Cheng Nuo
程諾
I think you can hide it by burning the memory card.
我认为你可以通过烧掉存储卡来隐藏。
I am currently looking for a manager to oversee your work.
我目前正在寻找一位经理来监督你的工作。
If you're hiding something, I'm sure I'll find it
如果你隐藏了什么，我相信我会找到它
In the end what happened?
到底发生了什么？
you don't tell me
你不告诉我
I let them tell me
我让他们告诉我
they won't help you
他们不会帮助你
only i can help you
只有我可以帮助你
what do you mean
你是什​​么意思
i know your identity
我知道你的身份
What did Yun Tianhong tell you?
云天鸿跟你说什么了？
he told me
他告诉我
I'm the same as him
我和他一样
Isn't there anything else?
难道就没有别的事了吗？
you?
你？
I think he knew I was a liar.
我想他知道我是个骗子。
Why are you putting up a sign for me now?
为什么现在才给我挂牌子？
i want to catch you
我想抓住你
is that so
是这样吗
You also have evidence
你也有证据
It's not too late to catch it now
现在抓住还不算太晚
I will take you to escape
我会带你逃跑
Why
为什么
Your role might be to find bionics.
你的角色可能是寻找仿生学。
you are different from them
你和他们不同
Every place is different, every place is different.
每个地方都不一样，每个地方都不一样。
You are a very important person to me
你是我非常重要的人
Lost someone important
失去了重要的人
don't lose it
不要丢失它
i want to protect you
我想保护你
Zhou Chen must be looking for us.
周辰一定是在找我们。
Quickly
迅速地
how far?
有多远？
Cheng Nuo
程诺
Don't want to go
不愿意去
i want to be here
我想在这里
Are you crazy or fake?
你是疯了还是假的？
There is only one result left here.
这里只剩下一个结果了。
Aren't you curious?
你不好奇吗？
Who am I?
我到底是谁？
Why am I a copycat?
为什么我是模仿者
But most importantly, I was able to stay in your eyes.
但最重要的是，我能够留在你的眼里。
do you know
你知道吗
Unless I know I'm a dummy
除非我知道我是个假人
I don't remember anything
我什么都不记得了
All I know is that I have a brother.
我只知道我有一个哥哥。
But I object to his memory
但我反对他的记忆
everything is blurred
一切都模糊了
I want to clarify all these things.
我想澄清所有这些事情。
if you can't find the answer
如果你找不到答案
I will not go
我不会去
what do you want to do?
你想让我做什么？
i want to go somewhere
我想去某个地方
Would you please come with me?
请你跟我一起去好吗？
elder brother
哥哥
run away
逃跑
you
你
Have you been here before?
你以前来过这里吗？
not any
没有任何
but someone told me
但有人告诉我
me and my brother
我和我的兄弟
used to live here
曾经住在这里
who
誰
Let's go in
我们进去吧
Run, An Qing
奔跑吧，安晴
come early
早点来
hurry up!
赶快！
Yasuharu
安晴
Quickly
迅速地
I won't make it in time
我不会及时赶到
rest assured
放心
elder brother
哥哥
freeze
冻结
let go
松手
elder brother
哥哥
Yasuharu
安晴
what happened
发生了什么
Do you remember anything?
你还记得什么吗？
No more bionics here.
这里不再有仿生学。
This is my home
这是我的家
me and my brother
我和我的兄弟
us
我们
I'm hiding here during the investigation.
调查期间我就躲在这里。
I hid there then
那时我躲在那里
Ever since my brother hid me
自从我哥哥把我藏起来
He even jumped out on purpose
他还故意跳出来
I have seen
我见过
He was dragged away by investigators
他被调查人员拖走
as you can see
如你看到的
Is that investigator here?
那个调查员在吗？
It's been many years
已经过去很多年了
It's normal if you can't remember
如果你记不住也很正常
let's continue.
让我们继续。
The people waiting for Miao Gan rushed in.
等待妙干的人冲了进来。
we have no chance
我们没有机会
why did you lie
你为什么撒谎
Not yet
还不说
Surveyed 2 years ago
2年前调查
you are here
你在这里
After 3 months of research
经过3个月的研究
We finally locked in on Sai Yuan City
我们终于锁定了西原市
A place where cottage thieves gather and hide.
山寨盗贼聚集、藏身的地方。
Some of them were involved in injury cases.
其中一些人涉及伤害案件。
This is a military camp town
这是一座军营小镇
The location is remote and the surrounding environment is complex.
位置偏远，周围环境复杂。
This is history in our eyes
这是我们眼中的历史
biggest action
最大的行动
I also hope this is my last scene.
我也希望这是我的最后一幕。
Many of these bionic animals have criminal records.
其中许多仿生动物都有犯罪记录。
Investigation focuses on personal safety
调查以人身安全为重
their existence
他们的存在
Damage the fundamental interests of the whole society
损害全社会根本利益
Do you understand it
你明白了吗
Clear
清除
Cheng Nuo
程诺
This time you will lead the way.
这次你将带路。
Yes
是的
make it look good
让它看起来不错
make out
认出
stop
停止
go
去
lie
嘘
come out
出来
what are you going to do
你会怎样做
Why did you arrest me?
你为什么抓我？
freeze
冻结
let go
松手
go
去
come out
出来
sit down
坐下
It was all my mother's fault back then.
那时候都是妈妈的错。
I'm very radical about androids.
我对仿生人非常激进。
A lot happened during that time
那段时间发生了很多事情
I'm like a devil
我就像一个恶魔
I do not want to say
我不想说
so i tell you i
所以我告诉你我
what happened
发生了什么
An Qiu
安秋
Do not touch.
请勿触摸。
Such a long time
这么长时间
You're doing all the things you don't want to do.
你正在做所有你不想做的事情。
just exposed
刚刚暴露
is that so
是这样吗
You may also want to know the truth about your mother.
您可能还想了解有关您母亲的真相。
if i knew
如果我知道
I will never see your pain
我永远不会看到你的痛苦
An Qiu
安秋
only one answer
只有一个答案
The person you killed
你杀的人
Is it my brother?
是我哥哥吗？
Yes
是的
An Qing is
安晴是
Kang Qing, Kang Qing, have you seen it?
康晴呀康晴，你看到了吗？
Talk to me Jingchun
跟我说话 靖春
Mr. Shiro
四郎先生
joseki
定石
I haven't been here for a long time
我已经很久没来了
Someone was injured and stopped.
有人受伤并停车。
Someone is sitting injured
有人受伤坐着
Please be quiet
请安静
Blood flows out from behind
血从后面流出来
Go back and sit down to park.
回去坐下来停车。
please sit down
请坐下
There are people injured
有人受伤了
Sit now
现在坐
Please call your car to go to the hospital.
请叫你的车去医院。
do it quickly
快点做
jump off
跳下
Third brother must not hit Mr. Bai.
三哥绝对不能打白先生。
Mr. Shiro
四郎先生
take it outside
把它带到外面
Please let us out, Mr. White.
请让我们出去，怀特先生。
stop
停止
let it go
放开手
investigation
调查
Only one android died.
只有一名仿生人死亡。
I did it
我做到了
But I didn't know I was your brother.
但我不知道我是你的兄弟。
I don't ask for your forgiveness either
我也不请求你的原谅
but please give me a chance
但请给我一个机会
I really want to help you and escape
我真的很想帮助你并逃脱
I want to hide my identity
我想隐藏我的身份
when the errand is done
当差事完成时
How can I take revenge?
我该如何报仇？
Think back
回头一想
he is right
他是对的
Cheng Nuo
程诺
haven't seen you for a long time
好久不见
We finally meet again
我们终于又见面了